# **COLIN ROBINSON**

407-595-8578 colindrums@me.com @ColinRobinson72

4924 White Bud ct. Windermere, FL 34786

#### **Profile**

I am a professional drummer of over 35 years, currently employed by Cirque Du Soleil in Orlando, and formerly a full-time drummer for Blue Man Group of 15 years, ending only as a casualty of the pandemic. I am a teacher at Windermere Preparatory School, both for private lessons and as a teacher's assistant. I am fluent with Pro Tools as well, and have written several cues for TV including the following shows: The Bachlorette, All Girls' Garage, To The Rescue, and several others as I play other instruments as well.

## Experience

On Call Drummer, Cirque Du Soleil, Orlando, FL-2022-Present Playing drum kit and percussion for Cirque's "Drawn To Life"

Private Music Instructor, Windermere Prep, Windermere, FL - 2012 - Present

Teaching private drum and guitar lessons, and teacher's assistant for High School Band

Full Time Drum Kit, Blue Man Group, Orlando, FL — 2007—2020
Playing high intensity shows on drum kit, teaching and training new drummers, training the Blue Men to improve their drumming. I was also the interim Music Director for one year when our Director left to be on the touring version of our show.

Full Time Drum Kit, Blue Man Group, Toronto, ON — 2005—2007 Playing high intensity shows on drum kit

### Education

Humber College, Toronto, ON — Honor's Diploma, 1996 3-year Music program

## **Skills**

I am fluent in music theory, performance and technique. I am fluent in using Avid's Pro Tools. I also compose music in several genres including pop, rock, and hybrid orchestral. I am proficient in using the Apple applications Pages, Numbers, and Keynote, as well as the Microsoft equivalents Word, Excel, and Powerpoint. I am proficient at jumping out of planes also, as I used to sky-dive.

#### **Awards**

I have received the Woody Herman Jazz Award.

#### References

Josh Nelson - Band Directory at Windermere Prep: 812-887-4442 Brynn Baudier - Stage Manager at Blue Man Group: 504-957-3483 Kit Chatham - Full Time Drummer at Cirque Du Soleil: 678-612-8970